<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Catalogue</string>

    <string name="capybara_description">
        The capybara (Hydrochoerus hydrochaeris) is the largest rodent in the world, native to South America.
        It is a semi-aquatic mammal that is well-adapted to aquatic environments. Capybaras have a barrel-shaped body,
        short head, and a cap-like face with front-facing eyes and nostrils. They have webbed feet and dense, coarse fur
        that ranges in color from reddish-brown to grayish. Capybaras are social animals, forming groups called herds, and
        they are known for their gentle and docile nature. They communicate through vocalizations, including barks, whistles,
        and purrs. Capybaras are herbivores, primarily feeding on grasses, aquatic plants, and bark. They are excellent swimmers
        and often submerge themselves in water to escape predators or regulate their body temperature. In the wild, capybaras
        play a crucial role in maintaining ecosystem balance by grazing on vegetation and influencing plant growth.
    </string>

    <string name="chinchilla_description">
        The chinchilla (Chinchilla lanigera) is a small rodent native to the Andes Mountains in South America.
        Recognized for its soft and dense fur, chinchillas have a compact and robust body with large ears,
        and their fur can vary in color from gray to beige. Chinchillas are crepuscular, meaning they are most active during
        dawn and dusk. They have large, dark eyes and a well-developed sense of hearing. Chinchillas are social animals, and in
        the wild, they live in colonies. As pets, chinchillas require special care, including dust baths to maintain their fur,
        as well as a diet rich in fiber. They have a lifespan of up to 20 years in captivity and are known for their playful and
        curious behavior. Chinchillas are herbivores, consuming a diet of hay, pellets, and fresh vegetables.
    </string>

    <string name="guinea_pig_description">
        The guinea pig (Cavia porcellus), also known as cavy, is a domesticated rodent that originated from the Andes region
        in South America. Guinea pigs have a compact body with a rounded head, short legs, and a short tail. They are social
        and gentle animals, often kept as companions or pets. Guinea pigs communicate through various vocalizations, including
        squeaks, purrs, and chattering sounds. They exhibit a wide range of behaviors, including popcorning, which involves
        jumping and twisting in the air. Guinea pigs have a herbivorous diet, requiring fresh hay, vegetables, and vitamin C-rich
        foods. They are known for their friendly and sociable nature, often forming strong bonds with their human caretakers.
        Guinea pigs have a relatively long lifespan and can live up to seven years or more in captivity.
    </string>

    <string name="marmot_description">
        The marmot is a large ground squirrel belonging to the genus Marmota. These rodents are primarily found in mountainous
        regions and are known for their burrowing behavior. Marmots have a robust body with a short tail, strong claws, and
        distinctive facial features. They are diurnal, meaning they are active during the day, and hibernate in burrows during
        the winter months. Marmots use loud whistles as a form of communication, alerting others to potential threats. They are
        herbivores, feeding on a diet of grasses, herbs, and vegetation. Marmots play a crucial role in alpine ecosystems by
        influencing vegetation through their feeding habits and contributing to nutrient cycling. They are important prey species
        for various predators, including birds of prey and carnivores. Marmots are highly adapted to life in high-altitude environments,
        where they navigate rocky terrain and are well-suited for climbing and burrowing.
    </string>

    <string name="default_description">Default description for the animal.</string>

    <string name="detail_activity_label">Detail Activity</string>
</resources>
